看来网络是不会消失了
So it seems like this Internet thing is here to stay, huh?
你不说话也没关系
It's okay not to talk.
你们猜怎样
Hey, you guys, guess what.
巴瑞和明蒂要离婚了
Barry and Mindy are getting a divorce.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是怎么搞的
What is the matter with you?
-不  是巴瑞和明蒂  -抱歉
- No. Barry and Mindy. - Oh, sorry.
我一听到"离婚"  就以为是罗斯
l hear "divorce," l immediately go to Ross.
谁是巴瑞和明蒂
Who's Barry and Mindy?
巴瑞是我差点要嫁的人
Barry was the guy that l almost married,
明蒂是我最要好的朋友
and Mindy was my best friend.
当初他不就是被你跟她乱搞吗
Wasn't he cheating on you with her?
是啊  但只表示
But that just means
他做爱时睡死在她身上  而非我身上
he was falling asleep on top of her instead of me.
他们为什么会离婚
Why did they get divorced?
显然是那男的搞外遇被那女的逮到了
Well, apparently she caught him cheating on her with someone else.
很可悲对吧
Isn’t that sad?
天啊  要是我真的嫁给他
God, could you imagine if I actually married him?!
我的人生会多么不同
I mean how different would my life be?
我懂你的意思
I know what you mean.
我总是在想
l've always wondered how different my life would be...
要是我没有离婚会怎样
...if l'd never gotten divorced.
-哪一次  -第一次啦
- Which time? - The first time!
真的  想象一下要是卡萝没变成同性恋
Seriously, imagine if Carol hadn't realized she was a lesbian.
想象不出来  我一直想到女女
l can't. l keep seeing it the good way.
我肯定还在练控手道[空手道]
l bet l'd still be doing my karate.
我们婚姻后期  我经常练控手道
Towards the end of our marriage, l did a lot of karate.
好宣泄我缺乏...
It's a way of release the tension from...
缺乏某些"肉体"运动的多余精力
... not doing anything else physical.
也许你不念成控手道就没事了
Maybe the problem was you were pronouncing it "ka- ra- tay."
如果我还是很胖呢
What if l was still fat?
你一定不会跟我交往
You wouldn't be dating me, that's for sure.
-当然会  -少来了
- Sure l would. - Come on.
你们真的觉得我那么肤浅吗
You guys really think l'm that shallow?
不  我只是觉得摩妮卡太胖
No, l just think Monica was that fat.
要是我没被《我们的岁月》开除呢
Hey, imagine if l'd never got fired off Days of Our Lives.
卡萝又出现了
Hey. Hey, there's Carol again.
要是我有勇气辞职呢
What if l had had the guts to quit my job?
我没准就在帮《纽约客》写稿了
l'd probably be writing for The New Yorker,
拿钱搞笑
being paid to be funny.
现在的工作也很有趣啦
But my job's fun too. l mean,
明天...  我不必打领带
tomorrow...l don't have to wear a tie.
要是我答应了去美林证券上班呢
What if l'd taken that job at Merrill Lynch?
-什么  -美林证券
- What? - Merrill Lynch?
对  我有个客人在那里上班
Yeah, l had a massage client who worked there,
他说我有炒股票的头脑
and he said l had a knack for stocks.
那你怎么不去
Why didn't you take the job?
因为当时我相信
Because at that time, you see,
押韵的事情都会成真
l thought that everything that rhymed was true.
我觉得要是我去做股票
So l thought if l worked with stocks...
就得住地窖
...l'd have to live in a box
只能吃安眠药  养三脚猫
and only eat lox and have a pet fox.
这种股票经纪人的确不咋地
Yeah, you don't want that in a broker.
你们觉得如果人生真的如刚才所说的
Do you guys think if all those things happened,
我们还会在一起吗
we'd still hang out?
《老友记》第六季第十五集  一切皆有可能
天啊  瑞秋·格林
Oh, my God. Rachel Green?
劳勃·提尔曼
Rob Tilman!
不对  是我  罗斯
No, no, it's me. Ross.
对不起  罗斯·提尔曼
Oh, l'm sorry. Ross Tilman.
不是  是罗斯·盖勒
No. No, no. Ross Geller.
-对哦  莫妮卡的哥哥  -没错
- Of course! Monica's brother. - Yeah. Right.
-你好吗  -很好  我结婚了
- Wow! How are you? - Good. Good. l'm married.
我也是
Me too!
-结婚真好不是吗  -是啊  超棒
- lsn't it the best? - Oh, it's the best.
-莫妮卡好吗  -非常好
- So how's Monica? - Really, really great.
事实上她就在前面街那
Actually, she's right down the street.
要不过去打个招呼吧
You know what? You should stop by and say hi.
-好啊  -她会很高兴
- l would love to. - Yeah, She'd be so excited.
-好  -走吧
- Okay. - Come on.
等等  你是不是忘了付你
Wait, don't you have to pay for...
《巨乳女郎》的钱了
...Busty Ladies?
没关系
No, that's okay.
是有个小孩托我帮他买啦  不过...
Some kid asked me to pick it up for him, but l....
是吗  好吧
Oh yeah? Okay.
好了
Okay.
可是你不用把钱还给那个小孩吗
But! Don’t you have to give him his money back?
钱还给你  抱歉  还是别看黄色刊物了
Hey, here you go buddy. Sorry, no porn for you.
好啦  我们去找莫妮卡吧
Okay, let’s go see Monica!
莫妮卡  你还在跟无聊医生交往吗
So, Monica. Still going out with Dr. Boring, huh?
他才不无聊  他只是...
He's not boring. He's just....
只是比较低调
He's low-key.
-给  你的榛果拿铁  -谢谢
- Here you go, one hazelnut latte. - Thank you.
其实榛果不是果实
You know, the hazelnut, actually not a nut.
而是种子
lt's a seed.
还有谁能说出一种常见种子
Can anyone else name a well-known seed
被当成果实[疯子]的例子吗
that's been masquerading as a nut?
天啊  我想想看
Oh, dear God. Let me think.
你怎么了
What's the matter?
我又被退稿了
l got another rejection letter.
他们说我的东西很有趣
They said my writing was funny,
只是不符合《阿奇漫画》风
just not "Archie Comic" funny.
《阿奇漫画》是美国的一个著名漫画
亲爱的  我得回医院了
You know what? Honey, l gotta get back to the hospital.
好
All right.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Okay. Bye- bye.
对了  答案是巴西果
By the way, the answer is: the Brazil nut.
他的原问题是  "有东西比他还无聊"吗
Was his question, "what's more boring than him?"
对了  他的毛衣背心好帅气哟
And nice sweater vest, by the way.
打住  伙计们  他是个好人
Stop it, guys. He's sweet.
老兄  退稿的事真遗憾
Hey, man. Sorry about the Archie thing.
你要我给你点钱吗
You need me to give you some money?
我穷归穷  但骨气还是有的
l may have no money, but l still have my pride.
是吗
Really?
也许乔伊不必给你钱啊
Maybe Joey doesn't have to give you the money.
-电视明星都有助理对吧   -好主意
- TV stars have assistants, right? - That's an idea.
要是我请助理转交  你会收吗
lf l hire an assistant, would you take money from her?
不是啦  钱德勒可以当你的助理
No, Joey. Chandler could be your assistant.
他可以帮你回信给影迷
He could answer all your fan mail and stuff.
不错  就这么办吧
That would be great! Let's do that!
我有钱领  还有时间写作
l could use the money. It could give me time to write.
-那就行啦  欢迎加入  -感谢
- All right. Great. Welcome aboard! - Okay!
我现在要去上厕所啦
All right. Now, l need to use the bathroom.
不过我上厕所不用人帮
Since l don't need any assistance in there,
-助理你就休息吧  -好的
- take a break! - All right.
菲比
Hey, Phoebe.
-你猜怎样  -怎样
- Guess what. - What.
乔伊找钱德勒当他的助理
Joey just hired Chandler to be his assistant.
真好
That's so sweet.
等一下  等我一下
Oh! Hang on!
等我一下
Hang on!
说
Go!
不对  不对  我是说一到50点就卖
No. No, no. l said sell when it hits 50!
50是一个数字  在49后面
Five- oh! lt's a number! lt comes after four- nine!
没关系  没关系
No, it's okay. lt's okay.
一次错误可以接受
You're allowed one mistake.
开玩笑的  你当然被开除了
Just kidding. You are, of course, fired.
真可惜  我蛮喜欢她的
Oh, what a shame. l really liked her.
莫妮卡
Hey, Mon?
你看我遇见谁了
Mon, look who l ran into!
天啊  瑞秋
Oh, my God, Rachel!
-你好漂亮  -你也是
- God, you look terrific! - So do you!
-你是不是瘦了  -你真贴心  居然注意到了
- Did you lose weight? - You are so sweet to notice.
没错  我瘦了3.5磅
Yes, l lost 3 1 \2 pounds!
记得我的朋友钱德勒吧
You remember my friend Chandler.
-那位是菲比  -你好
- And that's Phoebe over there. - Hi.
天啊  快坐下  坐下
Oh, my god! Sit down, sit down.
我们多久没见面了啊
How long has it been since we've seen each other?
上次是1987年  圣诞节第二天
1 987, the day after Christmas.
西恩·麦克曼的派对
Sean McMahan's party.
我弹了我的创作曲给你听
l played you one of my songs,
"星际求爱仪式"
you know, "lnterplanetary Courtship Ritual."
对  没错
Oh, yeah. Right.
-你还在玩音乐吗  -偶尔吧
- So, now, do you still do music? - Well, sometimes.
-找时间来我家  我弹...  -天哪
- You should come over sometime. l'll play you- -  - Oh, my God!
《我们的岁月》的主演乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives
居然走了进来
just walked in here!
瑞秋  他是我们的朋友
Rach, he's a friend of ours.
你们是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生的朋友啊
You're friends with Dr. Drake Ramoray?
要跟德雷克交朋友有点难呢
lt's hard to be friends with Drake...
因为他很忙  又是个虚构人物
...because of his busy schedule and the fact that he's not real.
我也可以把我的电子琴带过来
Hey, or l could bring my keyboard here sometime.
-他过来了  -乔伊
- He's coming over. - Joey?
好啦  拿去
l know. Here, here.
不是啦  这是我朋友瑞秋
No. This is my friend Rachel.
我们是高中同学
We went to high school together.
我好喜欢你演的戏
l...I love you on that show.
我每天都看
l watch you every day.
你的前妻明明想杀你
I mean when you took out your own kidney to save your ex- wife...
你还捐肾救她...
...even though she tried to kill you....
遇见影迷总是很开心
lt's always nice to meet fans.
-她不是疯子吧  -不是
- She's not crazy, is she? - No.
所以...你好吗
So how you doing?
等一下
Hang on.
等一下  等一下
Hang on. Hang on.
说
Go!
谁
Who's this?
好  你会爱上替我工作的
You're gonna like working for me.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
布伦蒂是什么鸟名字
What kind of name is "Brindy"?
我... 随便
I...Whatever...
闭嘴
Stop talking.
好  从今天开始你就叫琼安
All right, from now on your name is Joan.
姓给你自己选
You can pick your own last name.
我的笔不见了  你不会把它吃掉了吧
I can't find my pen. Did you eat that too?
-你在这里  -惨了  是老板大人
- There you are. - Uh- oh, it's my boss.
这是你今天该做的工作表
Alright. Here's a list of things for you to do today.
我们会合作很愉快的  太谢谢你啦
And this is gonna be so great. Thank you so much.
我要去片场了  今天要接生双胞胎
l gotta go to work. l'm delivering twins today,
但只有一个是我的骨肉
but only one of them is mine.
"把衣服送去干洗  去拿我的维他命
"Drop off my dry cleaning. Pick up my vitamins."
教我怎么写维他命
"teach me how to spell vitamins."
把我的新牛仔裤穿软"
"wear in my new jeans."
你知道你是什么角色吧
You realize what you are don’t you?
什么角色
What?
你是他的小喽啰
You’re his bitch.
不   不
No, no! No!
等等  你不会是坐坏了我的巧克力棒吧
Wait! You didn't sit on my Kit Kats did you?
不是  股市小幅震荡
No, there was a little, little dip in the market...
我损失了1千3百万
...and l lost 1 3 million dollars.
不过巧克力棒没事吧
But the Kit Kats are all right?
怎么办   怎么办
What am l gonna do? What am l gonna do?
通知公司  我会被杀
l can't call my office, they'll kill me.
通知客户  他们会自杀
l can't call my clients, they'll kill themselves!
-妙啊  现在还胸口痛  -什么
- Great, now my chest hurts. - What?
我的胸口在痛
My chest hurts.
现在喘不过气来了
And now l can't breathe.
菲比  你是心脏病发作吗
Pheobe, are you having a heart attack?
如果是  左臂会来回抽痛吗
lf l were, would l have shooting pains up and down my left arm?
-会  -那就是了
- Yes. - Then, yes. That is what l'm having.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
好了  这只手废了
Okay, this thing is useless.
你能帮我打电话叫救护车吗
So will you dial 911 for me?
别这样  菲比  没那么糟糕
Come on, Pheebs, it's not that bad.
一般人如果可以休息两星期
Most people would be excited
会放鞭炮庆祝呢
if they didn't work for a couple weeks.
一般人不喜欢他们的工作  我喜欢我的工作
Most people don't like their jobs. l love my job.
我才休息三小时
l've been not working for three hours,
我就快疯掉了
and l'm already going crazy.
我都想念琼安了
l miss Joan.
你心脏病发
Honey, having a heart attack is
是老天在告诉  你该放慢脚步
nature's way of telling you to slow it down.
我一直以为心脏病发
l always thought having a heart attack
是老天在表示  你该死了
was nature's way of telling you to die.
但是你不会死
But you're not gonna die.
你迟早会死
l mean, you are going to die,
但不是今天
but you're not gonna die today.
我去死了算了
l wish l was dead.
我们出去走走
Let's take a walk.
你应该考虑去替
Maybe you should consider writing for
《讲话不经大脑》杂志写稿
Talking Out of Your Ass magazine.
你最近怎么样
So what's going on with you?
我练控手道练得更勤了
Well, l've been doing a lot more of my karate.
-跟卡萝还在无性期吗  -对啊
- Still a dry spell with Carol? - Yeah.
你们多久没上床了啦
How long has it been since you've had sex?
-上个周末...  -那还好嘛
- Well, last weekend... - Oh, that's not so bad.
就满两个月...
...will be two months...
放弃尝试后的两个月
...since l stopped trying.
也许你应该玩一点刺激的
You need to spice things up.
-例如什么  -不知道啊
- What do you mean? - l don't know.
你们可以玩玩情趣捆绑啊
You could tie her up. She could tie you up.
可以在对方身上吃东西
You could eat stuff off each other.
淫言秽语  3P  性爱玩具
Dirty talk, ménage à trois, toys.
角色扮演
Role- playing.
你当典狱长她当囚犯
You're the warden, she's the prisoner.
你当海盗她当村姑
You're the pirate, she's the wench.
好  我懂了
Okay, l think l got it.
或者你们都扮演股票经纪人
Or you could be two stockbrokers,
在证劵交易所里的交易大厅
and you're rolling naked on the trading floor...
赤身裸体在大家面前滚床单
and everybody's watching.
纯属虚构
lt never happened.
抱歉
Sorry.
帮乔伊工作得怎么样
So how's things go with Joey?
很好  他现在都用暗号呼叫我
Just great. He beeps me now with codes.
1是"带吃的来"
One is:"Bring me food."
2是"有女伴  带吃的来"
Two is:"l'm with a girl. Bring us food."
3是"我迷路了  找不到吃的"
Three is:"l'm lost and l can't find food."
辛苦你了
Oh, sweetie.
这附近有吃的吗
ls there any food around here?
-她不会有事吧  -对  她在里面
- ls she gonna be all right? - Yeah, she's in there.
那就好
Oh, great.
脱裤子吧  看起来够软了
Go take off those pants. They look ready.
那里是布瑞帝酒吧
And all right, over there is Brady's Pub...
我行完医都喜欢去那里轻松一下
...where l like to unwind after a long day of "surgeoning."
好棒喔  还有呢
This is so amazing. What else? What else?
那是一个大型电视台设备
Well, that is a large piece of television equipment.
那是一个老男人
And that is an old man.
老男人  你好
Hey, old man!
参观完毕  要不要回我家继续参观
Alrighty. What do you say we head back to my place?
我很想去  但是不行
You know, l would really love to, but l shouldn't.
为什么  为什么
Why? Why...
世界不能停止转动
can't the world stop turning...
只要一下下  只为了我们
just for a moment, just for us?
那不是戏里的台词吗
lsn't that a line from the show?
对  不过
Yeah, but...
我或许说过同样的话  但是...
I may have said those things before, but...
只有这一刻...
...l never truly meant them...
我才是真心的
until now.
那也是戏里的台词
That's a line from the show too!
你看太多电视了
Okay, you watch too much TV.
乔伊  你要的现榨柳橙汁来了
Joey, here's the freshly squeezed orange juice you asked for.
谢谢
Thanks.
里面有果肉
There's pulp in that.
怎么了
Yeah.
我们不是讲过了
l thought we talked about this.
我不喜欢果肉  不要果肉
l don't like pulp. No pulp.
果肉不是果汁  我要纯果汁
Pulp isn't juice. All juice. Okay?
对不起  我就是喜欢果肉
l'm sorry. l guess l just like the pulp.
天啊  抱歉  我没顾及到别人的感受
Oh, my god. l'm sorry. l am being so rude.
瑞秋  你要喝汽水什么的吗
Rachel, would you like a soda or something?
钱德勒会马上去帮你买
Because Chandler will run right out and get it.
好啊  就冰红茶吧
Yeah, well, sure, iced tea would be great.
冰红茶
lced tea.
好  那您要什么吗
Okay. Anything for you, sir?
我刚才不是说了吗
Did l not just tell him?
钱德勒  你想替我工作
Okay, look, Chandler, if this is gonna work...
就要专心听我说话啊
...you have got to listen.
你要拿果汁泼我  对不对
You're gonna throw that juice at me, aren't you?
这不是纯果汁
lt's not all juice.
老婆  早上很好玩吧
So, honey, this morning was fun, huh?
我们洗澡时  我对你饿虎扑羊
Me hopping in on you in the shower there?
是啊  也许以后可以换一个
Yeah, maybe someday we could get a place
有两间浴室的房子
with two bathrooms.
卡萝  我在想或许
Look, Carol, l was thinking maybe....
我们可以玩一点刺激的
Maybe we can spice things up a little.
-怎么说  -卡萝  我们的性生活不美...
- What do you mean? - Carol, our sex life. lt's just not- -
-爸  -你在啊  小伙子
- Dad! - Hey there, little fella!
你要不要去穿鞋鞋
Why don't we get some shoes on you, huh?
你自己去房里穿鞋鞋
Why don't you show Dad how you can put your shoes on
-给爸爸看  好不好  -好
- in your room. Yeah? - Yeah!
说真的  我们的性生活...
Seriously, our sex life.
我想说或许...
l was thinking maybe, l don't know...
我们可以换个新花样玩玩
...we could try some new things, you know, for fun.
-像什么  -我不知道
- Like what? - Well, l don't know.
例如我们
What if we were to...
玩玩捆绑  如何
...tie each other up?
有些人会在对方身上吃东西
Some people eat stuff off one another.
不好
Yeah.
我们可以说淫声浪语助长情趣
You know, we could try dirty talk.
-我们可以玩3P  -这个我喜欢
- We could have a threesome. - l love that idea!
谁的故事被《阿奇漫画》采用了
Who sold a story to Archie Comics?
天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God, that's so great.
你是个发表过作品的作家了
You're a published writer.
真希望我准备了贺礼给你
l wish l had a present for you.
等等
Wait a minute.
我的最后一个巧克力棒
My last Kit Kat bar.
-我们一起吃好不好啊  -好啊
- You want to share it? - Okay!
钱德勒  我知道你很生气
Chandler, l know you're mad.
但我想跟你道歉
But I just want to say l'm sorry.
我太混蛋  太过分了
l was a total jerk. Completely over the line.
但我就是讨厌果肉
l just.... l hate pulp.
你知道莫妮卡是如何看待低脂美乃滋的吗
You know how Monica feels about low-fat mayonnaise?
那不是美乃滋
lt's not mayonnaise!
总之
Okay. Anyway,
我只想说对不起  这个给你
l just wanted to say l'm sorry, and here.
什么东西
What's this?
现榨的柳橙汁
Fresh- squeezed orange juice, with pulp.
-有你喜欢的果肉  -谢了
- Just the way you like it. - Thanks, man.
乔伊
Hey, Joey.
乔伊  钱德勒的故事被《阿奇漫画》采用了
Joey? Chandler sold a story to Archie Comics.
天啊  太棒了  恭喜
Oh my god! That's great! Congratulations!
是什么故事啊
What's the story?
也没什么
You wouldn't care.
只是个白痴的漫画故事
lt's just a stupid comic book story.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我最爱阿奇那票人了
l love Archie and the whole gang.
阿奇需要钱修他的老爷车
Well, Archie needs money to fix his jalopy.
但他不想跟瑞吉拿钱
But he doesn't want Reggie to just give him the money.
所以瑞吉就找他当助...
So Reggie hires him as his assist- -
当管家
As his butler.
然后叫他做一堆无聊事
And then makes him do crazy things...
例如叫他买不能有结块的奶昔
...like bring him milk shakes that can't have lumps in them.
等等  有点耳熟喔
Wait a minute. That sounds a little familiar.
这个故事画过了吧  我觉得我读过了呢
Did they already do that one? l think l read it!
莫妮卡  我一定要问
Monica, listen. l have to ask.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Okay, Joey Tribbiani
约我去他家
invited me back to his apartment.
他经常找女人去他家吗
Does he do this with a lot of girls?
对  经常  超级经常
Yeah, a lot. A lot, a lot.
而我是其中之一个幸运儿
And l'm one of them.
我真不敢相信  这可是乔伊·崔比安尼啊
l just cannot believe this. l mean, Joey Tribbiani.
瑞秋  你不必连名带姓一起说
Look, Rachel, you don't have to use his last name.
但莫妮卡  这可是乔伊·崔比安尼啊
But, Monica, come on, it's Joey Tribbiani.
所以你得连名带姓说
I guess you have to.
虽然与我无关
You know, it's none of my business, but...
但你不是结婚了吗  对啊
aren't you married? Yeah.
我有一点点希望我们还没有结婚
l wish we could just not be married for a little bit.
真希望我们能分开一下
You know, l just wish we could be, like, on a break.
可惜你们不是
Well, you're not.
你当然轻松  你又没结婚
So easy for you. I mean, you're not married.
爱跟谁上床就跟谁上床
You can have sex with whoever you want.
是啊  没错
Yeah, l can.
别以为我没有哦
And don’t think I don’t, because I do!
我一天到晚都有
l mean, all the time. You bet!
莫妮卡
Monica?
你有那方面的经验了吧
You've...you've done it, right?
当然有
Of course l have.
你以为我是个三十岁的老处女吗
What do you think, l'm, like, some 30- year- old virgin?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是个三十岁的老处女
You're a 30-year-old virgin.
要不要那么大声  怕后面那人听不到吗
Say it louder. The guy in the back didn't hear you.
我听到了
Yeah, l heard it.
我不是没有机会
lt's not like l haven't had the opportunity.
我只是在等完美的对象
I mean, l'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
我正在跟罗杰交往
l keep seeing this guy Roger.
他虽非完人
He's not perfect...
但是  或许我在想要不要将就一下
but l'm thinking maybe l should get it over with.
把我的"花蕊"给他
You know, give him my flower.
天啊  那就给吧
Oh, my God, do it!
你等得够久了
Honey, you've waited long enough.
你说得对  没错
You know what? You are right.
没必要把性看得那么严重
Yes. Sex doesn't have to be a big deal.
性爱不该有任何规则和限制
There shouldn't be all these rules and restrictions.
人应该随时随地
You know, People should be able to sleep
想跟谁上...
with whoever they want, whenever- -
瑞秋  我永远不会
Rachel, l'm never gonna think it's okay
支持你背叛你老公
for you to cheat on your husband.
你懂什么啊  处女
What do you know, virgin?
菲比
Phoebe?
厕所怎么有烟冒出来
Why is smoke coming out of the bathroom?
医生说可能会有这种副作用
The doctor said that could be one of the side effects.
菲比  把烟熄掉
Phoebe! Put the cigarette out.
不  那不是香烟
No, it's not a cigarette.
烟是从我身上冒出来的
The smoke is coming out of me!
-熄掉  -好啦好啦
- Put it out. - Okay, okay!
-真高兴有你们在  -躺好
- l'm so glad you're here. - Come on.
-我来接  -给我
- l got it. - Give it to me!
- l got it. - Give it!
喂
Hello?
她现在不方便接电话
No, she can't come to the phone right now.
好  没问题  再见
Right. No problem. Okay, bye- bye.
是公司吗   他们生气吗
Was it my work? Were they mad?
是杰克吗   他有嚷嚷吗
Was it Jack? Did he yell?
别紧张  没有人嚷嚷
No, just relax. Nobody yelled.
杰克只是打来问你有没有好转
Jack was making sure you were getting better.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
她被开除了
Yeah, she's fired.
你已经尽力了  卫斯理医生
You've done all you can, Dr. Wesley.
该放手了
You've got to let her go.
别了  好好安息吧
Goodbye and Godspeed, Hope Brady.
且慢  卫斯理
Not so fast, Wesley.
拉莫瑞
Ramoray!
没错  卫斯理
That's right, Wesley.
我只是来说
l just stopped by to say that
你不配当真正的医生
you're not a real doctor.
那个女人的脑部好得很
And that woman's brain is fine.
太好了
Oh, thank God.
-霍普  霍普  -德雷克
- Hope? Hope? - Drake.
霍普  你不会死
You're not dying, Hope.
你会从此过着幸福快乐的日子
You're gonna live a long, healthy life.
与我共度一生
With me.
德雷克
Oh, Drake.
好  我决定了
Okay.
好
Here we go.
乔伊  我是瑞秋
Hi, Joey? lt's Rachel.
我明天晚上有空
l am free tomorrow night.
没问题  我可以带三明治去
Yeah, sure, sure, l can bring some sandwiches.
亲爱的
So, honey, this...
关于玩3P的事
...this threesome thing?
第三人  我们该从何找起
I mean, how are we even gonna start to find- - ?
我把我认识的女人中
Actually, l'm making a list of women l know
可能有兴趣的女人列了个表
who might be into doing this.
天啊
Boy.
有人有认真做功课哦
Someone's been doing their homework.
是啊  我知道我列了两次盖尔·罗斯坦
Yeah, l know Gail Rosten is in there twice...
但是她好...
...but she is so....
我知道
Oh, l know.
光是用讲的  就让我有点...
You know, just talking about it
有点...
is getting me kind of....
我也是
l know. Me too.
是吗  班已经睡了
l think Ben's asleep.
我觉得我们最好...
You know, l think it'll be better
-多储存精力  -有道理
- if we just save it. - Yeah.
也对  储存精力  没问题
Right. Save it. l can do that.
你为什么老是戴着那顶帽子
Why do you always wear that dumb hat?
送报要迟到了吗
What, you late for your paper route?
"琼斯先生太太  报纸来了"
"Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Jones. Here's your paper."
"抱歉砸破你们的窗户"
"l'm sorry about your window."
菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
好点了吗
How's it going?
我得离开这张床
l've got to get out of this bed.
我快疯掉了  疯掉了
l'm going crazy here! Crazy!
喝吧  宝贝
Here you go, sweetie.
这是什么  花草茶吗
What the hell is this, herbal tea?
我讨厌花草茶
l hate herbal tea.
-但我加了蜂蜜呢  -你喝才需要加
- Well, l put some honey in it.- You need honey in it.
她还不知道她被开除了  对吧
She doesn't know she was fired yet, does she?
对  医生说告诉她会害死她
No, the doctors say it may kill her.
你们两个女生在窃窃私语什么啊
What are you girls whispering about over there?
不过我觉得应该告诉她
But l think we should tell her.
菲比  也许心脏病发是上帝提醒你
Look, Pheebs, maybe this whole heart- attack thing is a sign...
该开始考虑转行了
...that you should start thinking about getting a different job.
现在是在比赛谁笨吗
Okay, what is this, a stupid contest?
优胜者已经揭晓了
Because we've got a winner here.
菲比  他说得对  31岁不应该有心脏病
He's right. People are not supposed to have heart attacks at 31 .
我知道  但不做股票  我还能做什么
l know. But if l didn't work there, what else would l do?
你以前喜欢弹吉他
You used to like playing the guitar.
弹吉他能发家致富吗  你跟你哥一样聪明
That was lucrative. Smart like your brother.
那按摩呢  按摩可没让你生过病
What about the massage thing? That never gave you a heart attack.
拿着六位数的高薪
Pulling in a salary in the high six figures...
跟帮恶心的裸男裸女按摩赚小钱
...or rubbing gross naked people for chump change.
我该怎么抉择呢  我要如何抉择呢
What do l do? What will l do?
它真是栩栩如生呀
l mean, it's just so realistic.
就是啊
l know.
他的名字叫拍拍
His name's Pat.
拍拍狗
Pat the dog.
我懂了
l get it!
你...
Are you...
你要再来一杯吗
Ready for a refill?
我不该再喝了...
l probably shouldn't.
所以我要喝
So l will!
-感觉好像下雨喔  -很酷吧
- lt's like it's raining. - Pretty cool, huh?
要是你以为把鱼扔进去
But if you think you could put a fish in there...
不会卡进机器里
...and it wouldn't get sucked into the mechanism,
那你就错了
you'd be wrong.
可以借用洗手间吗
Can l use your bathroom?
就在那里面
lt's right through there.
要是一个星期前
You know, l gotta tell you.
有人对我说
lf someone told me a week ago...
我会在乔伊·崔比安尼家撒尿...
...that l would be peeing in Joey Tribbiani's apartment....
人生真美好  对吧
Yeah. Life's pretty great, isn't it?
希望你饿了
l hope you're hungry.
我们先吃生蚝
We're starting with oysters.
你知道生蚝的作用吧
You know what they say about oysters, don't you?
有寄生虫吗
They have parasites?
不是
No...
有人说生蚝有催情作用
Some people say that oysters are an aphrodisiac.
-什么人说的  -就是人嘛
- What people? - People.
有人说的
People say it.
过来
Come here.
生蚝是吧
So, oysters, huh?
然后再吃一些中东的粉蒸羊肉
Then we'll have a little Middle Eastern couscous.
我们可以
Something we can eat...
用手抓着吃
...with our hands.
有意思
You know what's funny?
-我们学到传染病时...  -别别别
- When we were studying communicable diseases- - No, no. No, no.
这样才性感
lt's sensual.
-我都不知道  -好  好
- Didn't know. Okay. - Okay.
别啊 别啊
No, no!
讨厌  抱歉  医院找我
I'm sorry, sweetie, it's the hospital.
菜都很棒  帮我留点好吗
The food looks great. Save me some?
我可不敢保证哦
l can't promise anything.
我们是要来真的  对吧
We're really gonna do this, uh?
看样子是
Looks like it.
其实呢
You know what?
要是你觉得很怪  我们随时可以停...
lf this is too weird for you, you can still back out anytime- -
-我来开  -好
-l got it! - Okay.
苏珊  你好啊
Susan, hi.
谢谢你的加入
Thank you so much for coming.
我怎么可能错过呢
l wouldn't have missed it for the world.
我是罗斯
l'm Ross, by the way.
罗斯  你好
Hello, Ross.
-我喜欢你家的布置  -谢谢你
- l love what you've done with this space. - Thank you so much.
真火辣呀
How hot is this?!
可惜在这里的是我  不是罗杰
l'm sorry you're here with me instead of Roger.
就是啊
Yeah, me too.
我可以假装成他
Well, l could make it seem like he's here.
关于粉蒸羊肉的小常识
"Here's some little- known facts about couscous:
粉蒸羊肉以前不叫这个  直到1979年
They didn't add the second 'cous' until 1979."
别闹了  一点也不好笑
Stop it! That's not funny!
-好啦  -对不起  只是...
- Okay. - l'm sorry, okay? lt's just...
今晚原本应该是件大事的
tonight was supposed to be a big deal.
-今晚要干嘛  -你不会想知道
- What was tonight? - You don't want to know what tonight was.
好吧
Okay.
今晚要干嘛
What was tonight?
今晚本应该是我的初夜
Tonight was going to be my first time.
跟罗杰吗
With Roger?
不只是跟罗杰吗
Not just with Roger?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
别激动  "只做过四次先生"
All right, relax, Mr. l've-had-sex-four-times!
跟四个不同的女人呢
Four different women!
次数则是多太多了
l've had sex way more times.
-几次  -九次
- How many? - Nine.
我只是在等完美的对象
l'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
这样很好啊
Good, good for you.
你真的觉得罗杰是那个完美对象吗
You really think that Roger's the perfect guy?
不是  但他也不算糟
No, but he's not a horrible guy.
我都跟女人那样介绍自己
That's what l tell girls about me.
钱德勒  我会死于处女之身的
Chandler, l'm gonna die a virgin!
你不会  你又贴心又善良
No, you are not. You are sweet and wonderful...
你一定会"做"到的
and this is gonna happen for you.
是吗  什么时候
Oh, really? When?
-你想跟我做吗  -好啊
- Do you want to do it with me? - Okay.
我是开玩笑的
l was kidding.
我也是
So was l.
乔伊  你真是个了不起的演员
Joey, you're such an amazing actor.
你怎么在拉莫瑞医生
How do you know where Dr. Drake Ramoray leaves off...
跟乔伊·崔比安尼间转换的呢
...and Joey Tribbiani begins?
拉莫瑞医生
Well, with Dr. Drake...
有现成的台词
...they always tell me what to say.
而乔伊
And with Joey,
就得靠自己编话说了
l pretty much have to make it up on my own.
你告诉我...
Tell me something, Joey.
-我刚刚从沙发上摔下来  -没错
- l just fell right off the couch there. - Yeah, you did.
-我没事  -来  坐好
- Okay. - Come on, here you go.
我问你一件事
Let me ask you a question. Yeah.
上一次
When was the last time...
别人称赞你美丽  是多久以前了
...someone told you just how beautiful you are?
我的手麻了
l can't...I can't feel my hands.
来  手给我
Come on. Come here.
-我们不能这么做  -没错
- We can't do this. - No.
-吃生蚝吗  -好
- Oyster? - Yeah.
要是我们"做"了
lf... if we did do this,
我压力会很大
there'd be a lot of pressure on me, you know.
因为你等了这么久
Because you've waited a long time,
我不想让你失望
and l wouldn't want to disappoint you.
但是我没得比较啊
But you see, l have nothing to compare it to.
就算你很逊  我也不会知道啊
Even if you were horrible, how would l know?
这个想法不错
l do like that.
我压力更大
lt's harder for me.
得跟另外四个女人比
l have four women to compete with.
其实只有三个啦
Well, if it helps, there were only three.
-所以只有今晚对吧  -那当然
- So it'd just be for tonight, right? - Absolutely.
只是朋友在帮朋友的忙
lt would just be one friend helping out another friend.
别说了  不行
Stop it. We're not doing this.
-来做吧  -不行...
- Let's do it! - No!
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay! - Okay!
你有招数吗
Do you have any moves?
我是有几招啦
l have some moves.
-我没任何招  -没问题
- l have no moves.- Okay.
你在干什么啊
Okay, what you doing there?
对不起  真的太奇怪了
l'm sorry, this is just too weird.
是啊  还是算了
Yeah, let's just forget it.
-要是我关灯呢  -试试
- What if l turn out the lights? - Okay.
爽啊
Oh, yeah.
-钱德勒  -怎么了
-Chandler? - Yeah.
那是沙发
That's the couch.
我知道
I know.
天啊  太赞了
Oh, my God!
我知道
l know!
告诉你
l'll tell you something.
我们一定要再来一次
We are gonna do that again!
没问题
Okay.
早安
Morning.
-对喔  -没错
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
天啊
Oh, God.
居然让乔伊·崔比安尼  听到我吐的声音
Oh, l can't believe Joey Tribbiani heard me throw up.
-他还有看到一点呢  -不会吧
- He actually saw you a little bit too. - No.
天啊  我们没有...没有...
Oh, God, we...we didn't...?
没  没  没
No, no, no.
看完怎么可能有兴致
Not after seeing that.
我真是很糟糕
God, l'm just a horrible person.
-为什么  -因为我已经结婚了
- What? Why? - Because l'm married.
没错  我是有夫之妇
That's right, l'm a married woman.
还跑到一个电视明星家搞外遇
l came to a TV star's apartment to have an affair.
别傻了
That's ridiculous.
我才不是明星
l'm not a "star."
只是一般的名演员
l'm just a regular famous actor.
而我是个很糟糕的人
And l'm a horrible, horrible person.
瑞秋  你别再自责了
Rachel, will you stop saying that?
瞧
Hey, look.
你记不记得卡普丽丝临死前
Remember on the show when Capri was dying?
-给了我...  -石洞里的戒指  记得
- And she gave me--  - The ring from the cave. Yeah.
好...天啊  你可以留着它
Oh, my God! They let you keep that stuff?
当然  只要不被发现
Sure. As long as they don't find out,
想留什么都行
you can keep whatever you want.
我要把它送给你
And l want you to have it.
-不要...  -要
- No, l couldn't. - Yes, yes!
你每次看到它
Every time you look at it...
就要想起你是个好人
...l want you to remember that you are a good person, ok?
你有机会外遇
Now, you had the chance to cheat...
而且还是跟我
...and with me.
但是你没有
But you didn't.
这就是这枚戒指的意义
And that's what this ring stands for.
我以为它是代表
But l thought that ring stood for
卡普丽丝对哥哥永不止息的爱
Capri's undying love for her brother.
-你到底要不要  -我要
- Look, you want the ring or not? -Yes.
你醒了  太好了
Hey, look at you! You're up!
我想去走一走
l thought l'd try to take a walk.
你们帮我倒杯水  我马上回来
Will you pour me some water? l'll be back soon.
你不会是想打公共电话回公司吧
You're not gonna use the pay phone to call work, are you?
不是  我已经学到教训了
No. l've learned my lesson.
快点  动作快
Let's go! Come on! Move it!
菲比  动作快点
Phoebe, come on!
鞋子  公事包  谢了
Shoes, briefcase. Thanks, Lou.
祝你的胆囊早日康复
Good luck with the gallbladder.
乔伊
Hey, Joe, did...
你...你玩过3P吗
...did you ever have a threesome?
罗斯  我觉得卡萝很漂亮
Look, Ross, l think Carol's great,
我也相信你很有魅力  但是...
and l'm sure you're very attractive man, but....
不是  我之所以问你是因为...
No. The reason l'm asking is that...
我昨晚貌似玩了3P
...l sort of had one last night.
你  对
You? Yeah.
漂亮  如何  过瘾吗
All right. So? Was it amazing?
还...
lt was...lt was...
好啦
...okay.
只有还好  你的玩法对吗
Just okay? Did you do it right?
感觉就好像自己在参加派对时
Look, it's just, did you ever go to a party
觉得现场有我没我都一样
and think "would anyone really miss me if l weren't here?"
不过
But still, Ross...
跟两个女人玩得再难玩
...your worst day with two women,
-也胜过其他日子  你懂吧  -那当然
- pretty much better than any other day. - Oh, I know.
只是
lt's just...
我玩的部分很快就结束了
...my part seemed to be over pretty quickly...
然后我就一直在旁边等
...and then there was a lot of waiting around.
你跟她们两个都有做吧
But you got to be with both of them.
好像没有
Not really.
我只有跟卡萝做
Just Carol.
-另一个没有  -没有  她一直把我踹开
- Not the other one? - No, she kept kicking me away.
-那样很讨厌  -就是啊
- You don't want that. - No.
至少你饱了眼福
At least you got to see a lot of stuff.
的确是大饱眼福呀
Oh, l saw a lot of stuff.
-你后来有点无聊吧  -有一点
- You get a little bored? - A little.
还弄了点吃的
Made a snack.
-你弄了什么  -就是三明治
- What'd you have? - Just a sandwich.
火鸡肉  加一点芥末酱
Turkey. A little mustard.
-好像很赞  -是很赞
- Sounds good. - lt really was.
跟你分享一下我昨晚跟一个女生全垒打
Let me tell you about this chick l scored with last night.
等等  就是你嘛
Oh, no. Wait a minute, that was you.
哎哟  我成了荡妇了
Hey, check me out, I’m a slut!
晚上要不要找事情做
So you want to do something tonight?
不行  罗杰医生又要来了
l can't. Dr. Roger's coming over again.
也对
Oh, right, right.
因为你还在跟他交往
Because you're still seeing him,
他是个好人
and he's a good guy.
我记得有一次...
I mean l remember a time....
你还好吧
Are you okay?
好得很...
Yeah, totally.
很好  你呢
Totally. Are you?
棒呆了  真的好神奇
Great. lt's so amazing.
上次罗杰来的时候
Last time Dr. Roger came over,
我好紧张
l was so nervous.
但是跟你做过之后
But after being with you, l'm like,
我变成"医生轮到我了吗"
"Can the doctor see me now?"
那是当然
l bet he can.
"我没有预约
"You know l don't have an appointment,
不过现在来个体检  一定爽歪歪"
but l sure could use a physical."
你真的没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事  别管我  我很好
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry about me, l'll be fine.
天啊  巴瑞
My God! Barry!
你说你周末都不在啊
You said you were going to be away all weekend!
没错  对不起  我回来早了
That's right! l'm sorry! l am early!
你们请继续
Finish, please!
惊喜  看看谁回来了
Surprise! Look who's back!
菲比
Hey, Pheebs!
通知警卫
Call security.
菲比  你不是被开除了吗
Pheebs, didn't you get fired?
我可不这么认为
l don't think so.
-菲比  -杰克
- Pheebe! - Jack! Hey!
-你来干什么  -我好多了  回来上班
- What are you doing here? - All better. Back to work.
但这个研究部猪头说我被开除了
This clown from research told me l was fired.
他应该好好研究嘛
He should do his research, huh?
你是被开除了
Well, you were fired.
才没有
No.
没有  我跟帮你接电话的人说了
l told that guy who answered your phone.
我没收到留言
l didn't get that message.
所以不算
So this doesn't count.
我先进办公室了
Anyway, l'll be in my office.
菲比  没有你的办公室
Phoebe, you don't have an office.
没关系  我就在这里工作吧
That's alright, l'll work right here.
这里很好  就在植物旁边
This is good. Next to this plant.
菲比  你听我说
Pheebe, listen...
你闯入我的办公室了
You're in my office.
听着  我替这家公司赚了很多钱
Look, l've made a lot of cash for this company. Okay?
而且是大钱
l am talking big bucks!
披索  日圆  卢布
Pesos! Yen! Rubles!
而我才犯了一个小错...
You make one little mistake- -
你损失了1千3百万元
You lost 1 3 million dollars.
原来一切都是为了钱啊
So now this is all about money?
我已经够...
You know, it's bad enough that....
别闹了吧
You have got to be kidding.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
-我心脏病又发作了  -什么
- l'm having another heart attack. - What?
我的心脏病又发作了
l'm having another heart attack!
叫救护车
Call 911 !
猪头
Dumb-ass!
菲比  你好吗
Pheebs, how's it going?
我被开除了  然后心脏病又发作了
They fired me, and l'm having a heart attack.
欢迎归队
Well, welcome back.
-罗斯  -瑞秋
- Hey, Ross. - Hey, Rachel.
乔伊·崔比安尼在吗
ls Joey Tribbiani here?
不在
Uh, no.
如果你见到他
lf you see him, will you please tell him
请转告他我在找他
that l'm looking for him...
这次我不会吐了
...and that this time l am not gonna throw up!
那可是个好消息
That-that’s always good news.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我  我很好
Me? l'm great!
我很好  我好得不得了
l'm fine! l'm so good!
但是你知道谁不好吗
But you know who's not great?
男人
Men!
-你是男人对吧  罗斯  -对
You're a man, right, Ross? - Yeah.
-坐下  -好
- Sit down. - Okay.
我问你一件事
Let me...let me ask you something.
婚誓对你们来说是个屁吗
Do wedding vows mean squat to you people?
为什么我们一说要出门  砰
Why is it that the second we tell you we are going out of town...
你们就跟邻居的遛狗小妹上床
...bam, there you are in bed with the neighbor's dog- walker?
我们很抱歉
We're sorry.
我说真的
No, seriously. Seriously.
婚姻的神圣性死哪儿去了
What has happened to the sanctity of marriage?
你昨晚不是才在乔伊家厮混吗
Didn't you spend last night at Joey's?
你是谁呀  侦探吗
What are you, a detective?
我不知道你和你丈夫怎么了...
Look, l don't know what's going on with you and your husband...
也希望那位遛狗小妹已经成年
...and what is hopefully an adult dog- walker.
但我要说不是全天下的男人都那样
Look, can l just say, not all men are like that.
有些男人愿意尽全力
There are men who'll do whatever it takes
只希望能挽回婚姻
to make their marriage work.
有些男人甚至愿意退到一边
And there are some men who will stand by and watch...
看老婆跟健身房刚认识的女人"2P"
as their wives engage in what can only be described as a "twosome".
火热得好像旁若无人
...with some woman she barely knows from the gym!
这些男人是谁啊
Who are these men?
就是我认识的一个人
Just men. A guy l know.
你可能要告诉他
Well, you might want to tell him
听起来他的老婆
it sounds like his wife...
是同性恋
...is gay.
她才不是...
She is not....
她是同性恋
She's gay.
天啊
Oh, my God.
她是典型的同性恋
She is so gay!
我真不敢相信
l can't believe this.
已婚者的"黄道吉日"啊
Good day for married people, huh?
很遗撼你老公不忠
l'm sorry your husband cheated on you.
很遗憾你老婆是同性恋
l'm sorry your wife is gay.
看来女人也没那么好
l guess women aren't that great either, uh?
去告诉我老婆啊
Try telling my wife that.
我可以进来吗
Okay to come in?
进来  吃饭  随你便
Yeah, come in, eat, whatever you want.
罗杰医生又被叫走了
Dr. Roger got beeped again.
我知道  你猜是谁找他
Yeah, l know. Guess who beeped him.
-什么  -我就是那个脾脏破裂病患
- What? - l'm the ruptured spleen.
你为什么要这样
Why would you do that?
因为你不该和他在一起
Because you shouldn't be with him.
你应该和我在一起
You should be with me.
是吗  对
Really? Yeah.
听你聊罗杰  让我好痛苦
When you were talking about Roger, that was killing me.
昨晚那件事不能过了就算了
Look, things like last night, they don't just happen, you know.
至少对我意义重大
At least not to me.
我跟另外两个女人在一起时
l mean, with the other two women...
共度春宵后  隔天早上
in the morning, you know, i was lying there
我就巴不得赶快去找朋友
l couldn't wait to go hang out with my friends.
但是跟你...
But with you...
我就是跟朋友在一起
...l was, you know, already with a friend.
-钱德  - 你知道你很可能不想跟我交往
- Chandler.. - I know you probably don't want to go out with me.
因为我太爱开玩笑
l make too many jokes,
也没认真谈过感情
l've never been in a serious relationship...
又不是个"医生"
...and l'm not technically a "doctor."
只有过一个女人  对不对
There was just one woman, wasn't there?
真的有两个
No, there were two.
-一个是我吗  -正确
- lncluding me? - Oh, yeah.
* 只要两次心脏病发 *
* It only takes two heart attacks *
* 就能让你认清 *
* to finally make you see *
* 一次死不了 *
* one of them won't do it *
* 但第二次会让你解脱 *
* but the second will set you free *
* 告诉你的恨意与愤怒 *
* Tell all your hate and anger *
* 是该道别了 *
* It's time to say goodbye *
* 我就会这么做 *
* And that is just what l will do *
* 只要我的老板们一死 *
* Soon as those bastards l worked for die. *